<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Manya Shah</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Manya Shah</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Project 1</title>
      <link>/project/project1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/project1/</guid>
      <description>About the Datasets For this project, I combined two different datasets. Dataset 1 consists of 2 categorical variables - Country and Development Status and 3 numerical variables - Literacy, Employment, and GDP (in millions of dollars). This dataset was obtained from the World Bank. Dataset 2 consists of 1 categorical variable - Country, and 2 numerical variables - Net FDI Inflows (in millions of dollars) and population of the country (in millions).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 2 - Manya Shah</title>
      <link>/project/project2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/project2/</guid>
      <description>About the Data For my project, I chose the ‘Heart Failure Prediction’ dataset from kaggle.com (https://www.kaggle.com/andrewmvd/heart-failure-clinical-data). The dataset has 153 observations, 6 numeric variables and 5 binary categorical variables. It aims to predict probability of the death of a person from heart failure based on various factors.
 About the Variables Age: numeric variable indicating age of patient in years Anemia: categorical variable indicating if patient has anemia or not (1=Yes, 0=No) Creatinine Phosphate: numeric variable indicating level of creatitine phosphate levels in blood Diabetes: categorical variable indicating if patient has diabetes or not (1=Yes, 0=No) Ejection Fraction: numeric variable indicating percentage of blood leaving the heart at each contraction High Blood Pressure: categorical variable indicating if patient has high blood pressure or not (1=Yes,0=No) Platelets: numeric variable indicating no of platelets in the blood Creatinine Serum: numeric variable indicating level of serum creatinine in the blood Sodium Serum: numeric variable indicating level of serum sodium in the blood Sex: categorical variable indicating sex of patient (1=Female,0=Male) Smoking: categorical variable indicating whether the patient is a smoker or not (1=Yes, 0=No) Death: categorical variable indicating if patient died from heart failure or not (1=Yes,0=No).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/</guid>
      <description> Check out some of my coding projects below:
 Wrangling &amp;amp; Exploratory Data Analysis
 Modeling, Inference, Prediction
  -- </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resume</title>
      <link>/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/resume/</guid>
      <description>    </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
